export const questions = [
  {
    question: "What’s my favorite food?",
    options: ["Pizza", "Biryani", "Pasta", "Momos"],
    answer: "Biryani",
  },
  {
    question: "What time do I usually wake up?",
    options: ["6 AM", "8 AM", "10 AM", "Whenever I want"],
    answer: "8 AM",
  },
  {
    question: "Which subject did I hate in school?",
    options: ["Math", "Science", "History", "English"],
    answer: "History",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s my favorite movie genre?",
    options: ["Horror", "Romantic", "Action", "Comedy"],
    answer: "Comedy",
  },
  {
    question: "Which app do I use the most?",
    options: ["Instagram", "YouTube", "WhatsApp", "Twitter"],
    answer: "YouTube",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s one thing I can’t live without?",
    options: ["Music", "Phone", "Coffee", "Sleep"],
    answer: "Music",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s my dream vacation spot?",
    options: ["Japan", "Switzerland", "Maldives", "Paris"],
    answer: "Japan",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I usually spend weekends?",
    options: ["Sleeping", "Watching shows", "Going out", "Studying"],
    answer: "Watching shows",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s my biggest fear?",
    options: ["Heights", "Spiders", "Public speaking", "Darkness"],
    answer: "Public speaking",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these hobbies do I actually enjoy?",
    options: ["Painting", "Coding", "Dancing", "Reading"],
    answer: "Coding",
  },
  {
    question: "Am I a morning person or a night owl?",
    options: ["Morning", "Night", "Both", "Neither"],
    answer: "Night",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s my favorite color?",
    options: ["Blue", "Black", "Green", "Red"],
    answer: "Black",
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these animals would I want as a pet?",
    options: ["Dog", "Cat", "Rabbit", "None"],
    answer: "Dog",
  },
  {
    question: "How do I deal with stress?",
    options: ["Sleep", "Music", "Overthink", "Talk to friends"],
    answer: "Music",
  },
  {
    question: "What’s my go-to comfort show?",
    options: ["Friends", "Stranger Things", "The Office", "Brooklyn Nine-Nine"],
    answer: "Brooklyn Nine-Nine",
  }
];
